p-bandai.hk 2012-12-25

# Privacy and Security｜Premium Bandai | Shopping from children to adults can enjoy Bandai official site

  * ## Privacy Policy

Bandai (H.K.) Co. Ltd. will take following measures on its private information protection policy. 

    1. Bandai (H.K.) Co. Ltd. follows laws and other regulations in maintaining the customer's private information.
    2. Privacy Statement  
The personal data collected in the membership registration form will be used by Bandai (H.K.) Co. Ltd., its subsidiaries, and/or associated companies. It is our policy to retain the personal data of our members for future product research and development purposes throughout your membership with Bandai (H.K) Co. Ltd. We are committed to ensuring that your information is secured. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.  
Under the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance, you have a right to request access to, and to request correction of, your personal data in relation to your membership registration. If you wish to exercise these rights, please write to our Human Resources Department.  
The personal Data that we have collected may be transferred to our subsidiaries and/or associated companies and/or other companies engaged in contractual activities on our behalf for the above mentioned purposes for which the personal data are to be used.
    3. In the case of obtaining a customer's private information, Bandai (H.K.) Co. Ltd. will follow appropriate and legal methods, will not obtain them in any illegal method, and will release and announce the purpose of its use to the customers as subjects of such private information. Whenever there is a need to access information outside the standard purpose of use, we will announce the new purpose to use only under the agreement with the customer.
    4. Bandai (H.K.) Co. Ltd. will conduct appropriate countermeasures to prevent illegal access, loss, damage, falsification and disclosure of the customer's private information.
    5. Bandai (H.K.) Co. Ltd. will conclude necessary contracts and appropriate supervision when commissioning to process a customer's private information.
    6. Bandai (H.K.) Co. Ltd. will take appropriate measures after confirming the person who requests the release, revision, suspension and elimination of the customer's private information.
    7. Bandai (H.K.) Co. Ltd. will not release private information to any third party except for the following reasons.  
(1)When the customer is in agreement.  
(2)When it is being released in situations where the customer is unidentifiable (such as statistic material).  
(3)When release or presentation is called upon under the law by a judicial or administrative body.  
(4)In situations where agencies are appointed to perform the processing of orders, delivery of products, credit card payments, system application and collecting questionnaires for businesses such as mail order.  
The required private information will be accessed only for the above purposes.  
Such agencies will perform these tasks only on the basis of agreeing to a nondisclosure agreement with the company.
    8. Bandai (H.K.) Co. Ltd. will continuously review and improve its effort to protect the private information.
    9. Under the Personal Data (Privacy) Ordinance, you have a right to request access to, and to request correction of, your personal data in relation to your membership registration. If you wish to exercise these rights, please write to our Human Resources Department.
    10. The personal Data that we have collected may be transferred to our subsidiaries and/or associated companies and/or other companies engaged in contractual activities on our behalf for the above mentioned purposes for which the personal data are to be used.

  * ## Use of Personal Information

PREMIUM BANDAI Hong Kong, owned and operated by Bandai (H.K.) Co. Ltd., gathers and uses personal information for, and limited to, the purposes listed below.  
Personal information gathered and used through PREMIUM BANDAI Hong Kong is submitted voluntarily by the User; and by submitting such information, you agree that we may use your information within the scope of this policy to: 

    1. carry out procedures necessary to proceed with the shipping of products and prizes;
    2. manage customer information and provide various customer services;
    3. provide information that are beneficial and necessary to you, in such forms as DMs, campaigns, questionnaire, and so on; and (It is, of course, your choice whether or not to give out your personal information,  
but please bear in mind that the lack of information may cause a limited access to some of our services.)
    4. contact you for necessary enquiry and confirmation on our end, as well as to collect customer feedback to better our services. 

  * ## Security

The server for PREMIUM BANDAI Hong Kong is secured by RapidSSL Digital Certificate.   
You will see that PREMIUM BANDAI Hong Kong is indeed owned and operated by Bandai (H.K.) Co. Ltd.   
Please rest assured that all the personal information you entered on this Website, which includes those required to place an order and send an enquiry as well as your User ID and Password, have been encrypted and safely transmitted to us through SSL (Secure Socket Layer) technology.

Please make sure and Sign Out after every session especially if you're sharing a computer, so as to safeguard your Password and other essential information against unauthorised access.
